Izzy: She’s beautiful.
Ben: Hi, Izzy.
Thanks for coming.
Izzy: Thanks for inviting me.
These photos are amazing, Ben.
You’re really talented.
I love the light in this one.
Ben: Oh, they’re OK.
Izzy: No really, it’s true. You’re a great photographer!
Ben: Thanks.
I’d love to see some of your photos, Izzy.
Andre: Yes. I’d love to see some of your photos, too, Izzy.
Izzy: Hi, Andre.
Andre: Hello, Izzy. How are you?
Izzy: I’m great.
Andre: You still take photographs?
Izzy: When I can. I’m very busy.
Andre: So, what are you doing these days?
Izzy: I’m working…as a bike courier.
Andre: That’s…interesting.
Yes, I taught Izzy.
She’s very talented – in fact, she was my best student.
Ben: You were a student at Tensquare, too?
Why didn’t you tell me?
Andre: Yes. But she didn’t finish the course.
One day she just stopped coming and…didn’t say why.
Izzy: I never stopped taking photographs.
But now I take them for me, and not for other people.
Andre: And how is that going for you?
It’s true. She was my best student and now she’s working as a bike courier.
What a pity.
Have a look at her photos.
Ben: Izzy!